ntorrents.net 2017-08-22

# Privacy Policy

General 

NTorrents Search Engine is powered by Google. This tool filter only the relevant results from Google Search Engine. Therefore, you are also subject to Google Privacy. You can read more here: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

What information do I collect? 

This page collects information from you when you use my search engine services. This system automatically records information about your url, IP address, browser information, language and date and time that you visit the site. Any information I collect from you may be used to improve my service (I continually strive to improve our site based on the information and feedback I receive from visitors.) and to measure the frequency of visitors (I analyze the data about visitors and our audience activity in this search engine). For privacy purposes, the service will not ask for your personal information such as you real name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information etc. Forget about it. When you send email or other communication to me, I may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve my service. 

How do I protect your information? 

I implement a variety of security measures to ensure that the information that I get from you is kept safe and secured on our servers. I do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating this website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. I may also release your information when I believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect mine or others` rights, property, or safety. Well, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

Cookies 

Cookies are small files that a site or its google search engine provider transfers to your device`s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site`s or website provider`s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. NTorrents is a search engine powered by Google. Google, a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google`s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other websites on the Internet. Visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. I use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences in the future. 

Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, I may include or offer third party products or services on my website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. I therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, I seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

Changes to my Privacy Policy 

If I decide to change this privacy policy, I will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy. 

Contact 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact me using the information below. Email: admin@ntorrents.net
